<hepcon>
  <logoImage></logoImage>
  <coverImage>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/vgvassilev/hepcon-config/master/art/ACAT2019_cover.png</coverImage>
  <notifications>
    <notification>
      <date>2018-12-14T12:25:30</date>
      <text>Welcome to ACAT2019</text>
    </notification>
  </notifications>
  <venueLocations>
    <venueLocation>
      <title>Allalin Hotel</title>
      <activity>Conference Center</activity>
      <address>Lomattenstrasse 7, Saas-Fee 3906, Switzerland</address>
      <latitude>46.111379</latitude>
      <longitude>7.929412</longitude>
    </venueLocation>
  </venueLocations>
  <sponsors>
    
  </sponsors>
  <floors>
    <floor>
      <title>The Plenum</title>
      <mapUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/vgvassilev/hepcon-config/master/art/ACAT2019_plenum.png</mapUrl>
    </floor>
    <floor>
      <title>Seminar & Breakout Rooms</title>
      <mapUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/vgvassilev/hepcon-config/master/art/ACAT2019_seminar.png</mapUrl>
    </floor>
  </floors>
  <wifi>
    <ssid>N/A</ssid>
    <password>N/A</password>
  </wifi>
  <twitterHashtag>#acat2019</twitterHashtag>
  <iacPersons>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Andrej Arbuzov</name>
      <subtitle>BLTP JINR</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Pushpalatha Bhat</name>
      <subtitle>Fermilab</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>David Britton</name>
      <subtitle>Glasgow Univ.</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Federico Carminati, SPC chair</name>
      <subtitle>CERN</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Gang Chen</name>
      <subtitle>IHEP</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Denis Oliveira Damazio</name>
      <subtitle>BNL</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Bruce Denby</name>
      <subtitle>U. Pierre et Marie Curie</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Junpei Fujimoto</name>
      <subtitle>KEK</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Clara Gaspar</name>
      <subtitle>CERN</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Gudrun Heinrich</name>
      <subtitle>MPI-Munich</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Andrei Kataev</name>
      <subtitle>INR</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Alexander Kryukov</name>
      <subtitle>SINP</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Jerome Lauret</name>
      <subtitle>BNL</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Milos Lokajicek</name>
      <subtitle>FZU Prague</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Daniel Maitre</name>
      <subtitle>Durham</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Axel Naumann</name>
      <subtitle>CERN</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Denis Perret-Gallix, IAC Chair</name>
      <subtitle>IN2P3/CNRS</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Fons Rademakers, LOC Chair</name>
      <subtitle>CERN</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Grigory Rubtsov</name>
      <subtitle>INR</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Luis Salinas</name>
      <subtitle>UTFSM</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Jose Seixas</name>
      <subtitle>Rio de Janeiro Federal Univ.</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Liliana Teodorescu</name>
      <subtitle>Brunel Univ.</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Gordon T. Watts</name>
      <subtitle>University of Washington</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
    <iacPerson>
      <name>Monique Werlen</name>
      <subtitle>LAPTH</subtitle>
    </iacPerson>
  </iacPersons>
  <locPersons>
    <locPerson>
      <name>Fons Rademakers</name>
      <subtitle>Chair</subtitle>
    </locPerson>
    <locPerson>
      <name>Federico Carminati</name>
      <subtitle>Co-Chair</subtitle>
    </locPerson>
  </locPersons>
  <codeConduct>
    The community of participants of the ACAT Workshop is made up of members from around the globe with a diverse set of skills, personalities, and experiences. It is through these differences that our community experiences success and continued growth. We expect everyone in our community to follow these guidelines when interacting with others both inside and outside of our community. Our goal is to keep ours a positive, inclusive, successful, and growing community.

As members of the community,

We pledge to treat all people with respect and provide a harassment- and bullying-free environment, regardless of sex, sexual orientation and/or gender identity, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, nationality, ethnicity, and religion. In particular, sexual language and imagery, sexist, racist, or otherwise exclusionary jokes are not appropriate.

We pledge to respect the work of others by recognizing acknowledgment/citation requests of original authors. As authors, we pledge to be explicit about how we want our own work to be cited or acknowledged.

We pledge to welcome those interested in joining the community, and realize that including people with a variety of opinions and backgrounds will only serve to enrich our community. In particular, discussions relating to pros/cons of various technologies, programming languages, and so on are welcome, but these should be done with respect, taking proactive measure to ensure that all participants are heard and feel confident that they can freely express their opinions.

We pledge to welcome questions and answer them respectfully, paying particular attention to those new to the community.

We pledge to be conscientious of the perceptions of the wider community and to respond to criticism respectfully. We will strive to model behaviors that encourage productive debate and disagreement, both within our community and where we are criticized. We will treat those outside our community with the same respect as people within our community.

We pledge to help the entire community follow the code of conduct, and to not remain silent when we see violations of the code of conduct. We will take action when members of our community violate this code such as notifying a workshop organizer or talking privately with the person.

This code of conduct applies to all community situations online and offline, including the conference itself, mailing lists, forums, social media, social events associates with the conference, and one-to-one interactions.

Participants asked to stop any harassing behavior are expected to comply immediately. Attendees violating these rules may be asked to leave the event. Please feel free to contact any member of the Local Organizing Committee or Shih-Chieh Hsu or Toby Burnet) or any member of the International Organizing Committee (acat-iac@cern.ch). Contact will be kept confidential.
  </codeConduct>
</hepcon>
